sparkchess.com 2017-06-06

# SparkChess Privacy Policy

The SparkChess.com website, SparkChess®™ game and SparkChess®™ Multiplayer service are created by Armand Niculescu, who asserts all intellectual rights arising from the game. “SparkChess” is registered trademark of Armand Niculescu. The SparkChess®™ game is distributed by Media Division srl.

We are committed to protecting your personal information. We want our services to be safe and enjoyable environments for everyone. This page aims to help you to understand what information we might collect about you and how we use it.

### Information we collect

On the website we may collect non-personally-identifiable information such as operating system, browser and system capabilities.

For purchases, we collect name, email, product bought, IP address and country of residence. We do not collect, transmit or store credit card information on our systems.

Within the multiplayer service we collect the IP address and optionally email address.

### How we use the information

We may sometimes use non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site, to personalize our visitors’ experience or to offer products, programs, and services. We may also use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer products, programs, or services. We do not use the information to create profiles or to uniquely identify and track users.

We may use your email address to inform you about important product upgrades or to resolve account issues. At this time we do not send periodic newsletters. We will never sell or otherwise distribute names and email addresses to third parties.

We use IP addresses and country of residence to calculate taxes, to prevent fraud and also for multiplayer matchmaking.

### Your rights

You have the right to ask us what personally-identifiable information we have about you and to ask us to delete or modify this information. You must submit a request for this.

### Cookies

Cookies are small text files that store user preferences about a site. We may use cookies to store your settings and preferences regarding sparkchess.com. We do not track your visits to other sites. Here are the types of cookies we may use:

  * Preferences – we store your settings and preferences, e.g. whether or not you’re logged in or if you have performed certain actions so we don’t prompt you again, and so on.
  * Anonymous analytics – we use Google Analytics to analyse metrics like the number of daily visitors and technical information about their browsers, in order to improve the website. We do not collect personal information.
  * Third party advertising cookies – we use Google AdSense to serve ads, which are vital for us in order to be able to continue operating the site. Google has their own privacy policies, and we have no access to read or write these cookies. Google may use their cookies to anonymously target advertising to you on other websites, based on your visit.

### Collection of Information and Third-Party Sites and Sponsors

We do not disclose personally identifiable information to third parties. We use Google to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies and SparkChess may use information (not including personally identifiable information) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Third parties and/or SparkChess may be placing and reading cookies on your browser to collect information, in the course of ads being served.

### Security

We have implemented appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.
